So if you remember back to this section right here,
对于这部分
what we did was we threw in a view to basically give our calendar,
我们通过添加视图
give our app a little bit of padding from this status bar.
使日历（即我们的应用）与状态栏之间有一些内边距
We just gave an arbitrary height of 20.
我们随意地将 height 设为 20
But what we actually want to do now is make a real status bar.
现在我们将创建一个真正的状态栏
So what we'll do is up here,
转到这里
let's import status bar which is a component on the React Native package.
导入 StatusBar 它是 react-native 软件包上的组件
But instead of just using status bar outright down here,
但是并非直接在这里使用 StatusBar
what I want to do is I want to actually make our own custom status bar.
我想要构建自定义状态栏
So we'll come up here, will say,
转到这里
you'd ask your status bar and then what we will
输入 UdaciStatusBar
take in is a background color and then basically just everything else.
传入 backgroundColor 以及所有其他属性
So what we'll do is we basically want to wrap
我们希望将这个状态栏组件
this status bar component inside of a view that we can better control the styling on.
封装在一个视图中 以便更好地控制样式
So what we'll say is we'll give it an object as its styling.
为其提供一个样式对象
We have background color and then height is
设定 backgroundColor
going to be whatever height we need the status bar to be,
height 将是我们希望状态栏具备的高度
whether that's an iOS or Android it's going to be different.
在 iOS 和 Android 上将不同
So what's nice about expo is it comes with this thing.
expo 的好处是提供了这项功能
I say thing, I mean object called Constants which is coming from
也就是叫做 Constants 的对象
the expo package and it has on it a very convenient status bar height.
来自于 expo 软件包 它提供了非常便利的 statusBarHeight
So we don't have to worry about that.
因此我们不需要管它的
That will just work because expo knew we would need that,
能够直接运行 因为 expo 知道我们需要它
so it threw it in that we don't have to worry
我们不需要在这里设置合适的数字
about a magic number here like 50 or whatnot.
例如 50 或其他值
It's just coming from Constants.statusBarHeight.
直接由 Constants.statusBarHeight 设定
So now what we can do is we can render a status bar where you want it to be translucent,
现在我们可以渲染 StatusBar 设为 translucent
if I can spell that right,
拼写应该没错
and then the background color of this is also going to be background color.
backgroundColor 也为 backgroundColor
Then we're just passing along any props that we get.
然后传入所有的属性
So basically what we've done is we've created this wrapper for status bar.
这段代码的作用是为状态栏创建了这个封装器
And then now what we can do down here is instead of rendering this view,
然后在这里 我们将渲染 UdaciStatusBar
let's render a UdaciStatusBar.
而不是这个 View
We will pass it a few things.
传入一些参数
Let's give it a background color of purple and then we will
将 backgroundColor 设为 purple
give it a bar style of light-content.
将 barStyle 设为 light-content
This is going to make all of the items in the status bar white.
这样使得状态栏中的所有内容变成白色
So now when our apps reload you'll
现在 当应用重新加载时
notice that up here it is the perfect height for what we need.
这里的高度很完美 正好能满足需求
The actual background is purple and the items in the status bar is white.
实际背景色是紫色 状态栏中的内容是白色
So it looks a lot better than what we used to have.
比之前的界面看起来好多了